

## **SKILLS**

- Abap workbench, functions, Classes
- JAVA, Android, C, C#
- PHP, Https, HTML, Xml, Json
- Odata
- · Web services, Integration
- · CDS, Hna
- SQL, Open Sql, dba, database design

## **EDUCATION**

05/2009

King Fahd University of Petroleum And Minerals | Daharan, Saudi Arabia Bachelor. Computer Science graduated from KFUPM in [September 2009] and earned B.S. degree in Information & Computer Science (ICS).

Development, Network Architecture, Internet Protocol, Database Systems (3 courses), Java Programming (3 courses), Soft Computing, Data mining techniques and Artificial Intelligent. Elective courses include: Engineering Economic Analysis, Basics in Saudi Legal Environment. Designed face recognition system for my graduation project (awarded -A+).

# Hasan AlOdele

0503932915

hasan.alodele@yahoo.com

Eastern Province, Saudi Arabia

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Career in SAP NetWeaver 7.0. since 2010 ABAP: full stack developer, responsible for code development, enhancement, test, working with team lead and other team members from early blueprint stage to reach maximum satisfaction for stakeholders

Task Summary: High Level design prepared by functional consultant during blueprint phase and prepare the Low-Level Design to complete in coding in ABAP workbench in ERP SAP R/3 system, all through realization phase, final preparation phase, and continue until UAT & support phase.

### **WORK HISTORY**

05/2022 - 12/2022

Shras IT Solution
SAP ABAP Developer

 Aramco Project: Archibus Integrated facility Management System, Sap integration

06/2021 - 05/2022

Tech Mahindra

Sap Abap developer

- Contractor Passport Project, Aramco Mobile app to monitor manage, contractors Access permission, Gosi payments, industrial security blacklist, this project make using of ui5 application, Flatter for mobile application, as well integration with governments agencies, Moi, Moh.
- I handled Sap backend, support for Mobile and Ui5 teams::
- ✓ Abap dictionary. ✓ SQL db design. ✓ Abap workbench. ✓ r3 reports, ✓ schedule jobs. ✓ SProxy. ✓ Aramco Workflow.
   ✓ SEGW Odata. ✓ PI Api. ✓ RFC. ✓ Hna CDS. ✓ Push Notifications. ✓ Adobe QR
- backend take responsibility to build end to end Data migration functions with Hna, through PI/Po Middlewere

04/2018 - 06/2021

## multiple jobs

Freelance developer

at Hna travel agency, developed end to end Android application
to enhance consumer experience, Php dashboard, website & IOS,
later we had to shutdown. Our agency was providing third party
travel services, hotels, car rental, airline tickets, focus on Gcc
market. There I got experience from business prospective,
running dally activity in financial management, HR management
and stock management. I was also involved digital
advertisement and got deeper insights as to how we can use
analytics to reach the right audience.

08/2012 - 02/2018

### Ejada System

SAP ABAP Developer

- Aramco Projects:: Senior ABAP-SQL developer for BW in Domestic Sales Customers Dashboard Project.
- Senior ABAP-SQL developer for BI/BW in e-Recruitment Reports Enhancement Project.
- Abap, User Exits, ALV, Routines for Aramco Medical retirement Services.
- Ministry Of Finance: 6 months at 2017 support assignments, QA for government VAT system at General Authority of Zakat & Tax (GAZT) at Riyadh

02/2012 - 08/2012

#### Kaar Technology

SAP ABAP Developer

 Aramco Project, Trial Test Request (TTR), senior Abap developer, Workflow, Web Dynpro, QA

08/2010 - 02/2012

AlBilad Arabia

SAP ABAP Developer

· Conducted Abap and object-oriented programming using open-